Guide to the Hugh Heclo government policy collection, 1901-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Hugh Heclo government policy collection
  - Notes from a conversation with Mrs. Ann Whitman 6/26/80 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Interview with Maxwell Rabb (from tape) 6/26/80 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Notes on Interview with George Elsey 7/1/80 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - A Letter to the Next President (Box 28, Folder 10)
    While the document is not dated, it was written by Roy Ash and Mr. Reagan or Mr. Carter if he was to re-elected.
  - Some Thoughts on the Lyndon B. Johnson White House (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Some Thoughts on the Eisenhower White House (Box 28, Folder 12)
    by A. Nelson
  - FDR: Book Review (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Political Science Quarterly book reviewed, Hitler vs. Roosevelt: The Undeclared Naval War by Thomas A. Bailey and Paul B. Ryan 1979
  - The Origins of Massive Retaliation Spring 1981 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Management of Budgetary and Fiscal Policy making Fall 1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Political Science Quarterly
  - Eisenhower Group (Box 28, Folder 16)
    notes from a group interview
  - [Tape of Interview of] Luther Gulick 1 of 2 2/28/80 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Luther Gulick 2 of 2 2/28/80 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Bernard L. Gladieux 1 of 2 3/17/80 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - [Tape of Interview of]Bernard L. Gladieux 2 of 2 3/17/80 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Fred A. McNarama 12/3/79 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Dwight Ink 1 of 2 (McGeary) 3/18/80 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Dwight Ink 1 of 2 (McGeary) 3/18/80 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Dwight Ink 1 of 2 (Heclo) 3/18/80 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Dwight Ink 2 of 2 (Heclo) 3/18/80 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - [Tape of Interview of] Jarold Kieffer 1 of 3 1/28/80 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    tapes 2 and 3 missing from collection
  - [Tape of Interview of] John D. Millett 1 of 2 1/29/80 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    2nd tape missing from collection